主演：迈克尔・福克斯
拜托
Please.
拜托，不要伤害我
Please don't hurt me.
别动手！她太年轻了！
It's wrong! She's too young!
肉体的罪恶会毁了她
The sins of the flesh will ruin her.
拜托不要伤害我！拜托！
Please don't hurt me! Please!
邪恶的人必付出代价
The wicked will be punished.
『恐 怖 幽 灵』
命案重演！本周第三宗悬案
费尔沃特镇的居民怎么了？
恰克修斯：享年37岁
在过去4年来…
"The mystery heart condition...
令30余人丧命的心脏病…
"that has killed over 30 people in less than four years...
“再度夺去另一人的性命”
"has claimed another victim. "
医界对于健康的人们…
"Doctors are baffled"as to why seemingly fit and healthy people...
突然间因严重心脏病丧生而感到不解
"are suffering massive heart attacks.
许多费尔沃特镇的居民都认为…
"Many of Fairwater's residents are claiming that the shadow of Death...
“死亡的阴影再一次笼罩大地”
"has once again descended on the town. "
死亡的阴影是什么鬼话？我不喜欢
What's this shadow of Death stuff? I don't like it.
瑞斯琼斯小姐，那是居民说的
It's what they're saying, Miss Rees-Jones.
镇上很多人都吓坏了
There's a lot of scared people out there.
几十年来，费尔沃特镇就等于死亡…
"For decades"the name of Fairwater has been synonymous with Death...
1964年布莱德利和巴特利凶案后就一蹶不振
"following the infamous 1964 Bradley-Bartlett murder spree.
30年后，镇上死亡人数再度上升…
"Thirty years later as the death toll steadily rises...
看来死神这回再度…
"it appears the Grim Reaper has once again returned...
“来到了悠静的费尔沃特镇”
"to the quiet streets of Fairwater. "
喔，不
Oh, no.
不，史帝夫
Steve, no.
要不同的观点，写创新的报导给我看
I asked for a new angle. Now give me something fresh.
我想知道人们怎么看待这桩悲剧
I want to see the human face of this tragedy.
到镇上去，跟受害家属谈一谈
Get out there. Talk to the families.
我想知道这件事对当地社区有什么影响
I want to know how this thing has impacted on the local community.
是，瑞斯琼斯小姐
Yes, Miss Rees-Jones.
史帝夫，不要再把死亡拟人化
And Steve, no more references to death as a person.
家属的朋友？真是太遗憾了
Friend of the family? Really such a shame.
法兰克班尼斯特，灵媒调查员
“和你的亲人联系”
离开，快点给我离开这里
Get out. Go on, get out. Go on.
快走
Get out.
修斯今天将入土
墓园
导演：彼得・杰克逊
该死
Damn.
喔，不！
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
喔，老天爷啊！
Oh, my God!
喔，我的天哪，怎么会发生这种事
Oh, my God,I don't believe this. This is not happening.
你毁了我前院的草皮
My lawn, you ruptured my lawn.
Whoa.
嘿，你好
Hey. How you doing?
打通电话给我，我一定会赔偿损失
Just give me a call. I'll pay for the damages.
少说废话，你当然要…
You're damn right you're gonna pay...
我要告死你
'cause I'm gonna sue your ass.
不要告到法庭上嘛
Now let's not get litigious, all right?
寄帐单给我就好
Just send me a bill.
“灵媒调查员法兰克班尼斯特”？
"Frank Bannister, Psychic Investigator"?
没错　　还真不错
That's right. Well, that's a good one.
你怎么不看路啊？死蠢蛋
How come you didn't see the corner coming? You stupid moron.
他妈的狗屁！
This is goddamn bullshit!
老兄，你听好，我绝不会轻易放过你
Listen, buddy, this is gonna cost you big time.
帮我付维修篱笆的钱，听到没？
You're paying for a new fence, you hear me?
最好把我的草皮给翻新
I want this lawn completely resurfaced.
要不然你就…
Or we're going to talk about a...
巴索！我的巴索
Budzo! My Budzo.
我把你的车牌号记下来了，你这混帐！
I got your license plate number, you bastard!
疗养院-费尔沃特医院
这是私人产业
This is private property.
布莱德利太太？医护中心的林斯基医生
Mrs. Bradley? I'm Dr. Lynskey. I work at the medical center.
你才不是，我对那儿熟得很
No, you don't. I know who works there.
我3个月前刚就职
I started there three months ago.
卡明医生才是我的医生
Dr. Kamins is my personal physician.
是，卡明医生今天去参加葬礼
Yes, well, Dr. Kamins is attending a funeral...
所以我帮他代班
and I'm seeing his patients today.
她本来在切蔬菜，不过刀子滑掉了
She was cutting the vegetables and the knife slipped.
缝几针应该就不会有大碍
Well, a couple of stitches and she'll be fine.
我载你到医院去
I'll drive you to the clinic.
想都别想
That's impossible.
她伤口很深　　那就给她抗生素
It's a deep cut. Then leave her some antibiotics.
妈，拜托　　派翠亚从不出家门
Mother, please. Patricia never leaves the house.
但好痛　　快给我回房间去！
But it hurts. To your room, this instant!
等一下
Wait, just a minute.
谁这样对待你？
Who did that to you?
林斯基医生，你最好快离开
I think you'd better go now, Dr. Lynskey.
你不认识我女儿吧？
You don't know who my daughter is, do you?
绝不能相信派翠亚　　什么？
Patricia's not to be trusted. I beg your pardon?
我随时都可以报案检举她
I can have her locked up anytime I want to.
他们说她是帮凶
They said she was an accessory after the fact.
我知道真相
I know the truth.
发生的是冷血谋杀案
It was cold-blooded murder.
血淋淋的27分钟内…
In the space of 27 blood-soaked minutes...
12位无辜的民众…
12 innocent people gunned down...
不幸被护理员强尼查尔斯巴特利击毙
by hospital orderly John Charles Bartlett.
病人、医护人员、访客…
Patients, medical staff, visitors...
没人逃过费尔沃特疗养院杀人魔…
no one was spared in this madman's rampage...
无情的暴行
through Fairwater Sanatorium.
就连医院的小教堂都成了命案现场…
Not even the hospital chapel provided sanctuary...
当时在祈祷的民众也难逃一劫
as those in prayer were gunned down on their knees.
拜托一下！
For heaven sakes!
拜托，我们是记者，本来就该报导新闻
We're reporters, for God's sakes. We're supposed to get the news.
一宗看来不合逻辑的犯罪案
A seemingly senseless crime.
巴特利杀人的动机，至今仍是一团谜
Bartlett's motive remains a mystery to this day.
强尼巴特利
Johnny Bartlett.
他看起来就像魔鬼
He's got a demonic look on his face.
能跟你说几句吗？　待会儿
Can I talk to you? Later.
强尼，有何意见？
Any comments, Johnny?
先生，我得了12分
Got me a score of 12, sir.
比史达魏德还多一个
That's one more than Starkweather.
6年前，查尔斯史达魏德…
Six years earlier, Charles Starkweather...
在内布拉斯加州大开杀戒，使11人丧生
had murdered 11 people in a Nebraska killing spree.
看来我是头号大众敌人！
Guess that makes me public enemy number one!
年仅15岁的派翠亚安布莱德利…
Fifteen-year-old Patricia Ann Bradley...
医院管理人之女…
daughter of the hospital administrator...
被控为本谋杀案帮凶
was also implicated in the killings.
她对杀人狂巴特利非常有好感
She was madly in love with the psychopath, Bartlett.
是她
That's her.
我今天下午去了她家
I was in her house this afternoon.
杀人狂与精神变态者
宝贝，太好了
Well, that's just terrific, honey.
我们才搬到这儿3个月…
We've been in town for three months...
你就已经跟杀人狂做朋友了
and you're making friends with the Manson Family.
2千2百伏特的电流…
2,200 volts of electricity...
将毫无悔意的杀人魔强尼巴特利置于死地
ended the life of Johnny Bartlett, the unrepentant killer.
电椅启动时，他尖叫说…
As they threw the switch he was heard to scream:
“我得了12分，谁也比不过”
"I got me a score of 12. Beat that. "
许多人都觉得派翠亚安布莱德利…
In what some considered a miscarriage of justice...
当初被判终生监禁并不公平…
Patricia Ann Bradley was sentenced to life imprisonment...
因为从未有法律判决证实她真有涉嫌…
although it was never proven that she actively participated...
这桩谋杀案
in the killings.
5年前，州长有条件释放…
Five years ago, Patricia Bradley was granted a conditional release...
派翠亚布莱德利
by the State Governor.
如今她回到老家，过着隐居的生活…
Today she lives a reclusive life back in the family home...
电巴特利的时候，也该把她给电死
Should've fried her when they fried Bartlett.
她当年才15岁耶
She was 15 years old, you know.
只不过是爱错了人
She just fell in love with the wrong guy.
谁都可能犯这种错
It could happen to anyone.
宝贝，别再去那里
Sweetie, I don't want you going back up there.
那地方让我觉得很不舒服
The place gives me the creeps.
我觉得你真的没必要…
I really don't think that you should...
拜托一下嘛
Come on, honey.
我好像有点寂寞喔
I think Tiger's getting a little lonely.
猜我今晚做了什么？
Guess what I did tonight, honey?
我在石中剑餐厅订了位
I made reservations at Excalibur.
宝贝，你不记得了？
Don't you remember, sweetheart?
这个星期二是我们的周年纪念
It's our anniversary this Tuesday.
我还订了我们最喜欢的位置
I even got our favorite table.
不错吧，小呆呆？
Yeah? You silly-willy?
这怎么会在这儿？
What the hell is this doing here?
我明明就撕掉了
I thought I tore this up.
他有回到家里来吗？　谁？
Did he come back to the house? Who?
把我们围篱撞烂了的那个蠢蛋！
That moron that tore up my fence!
救救我啊！雷，救救我！
Help! Ray, help.
他是活的
He's alive.
雷！
Ray!
雷，救我下来！
Ray, get me off!
你这个变态！
You sick thing!
露西，我不要那骗子上门
Lucy, I don't want that con man in my house.
一定有什么合理的解释吧
There's gotta be some kind of rational explanation for all this.
我可不想听那个通灵蠢蛋的话
I just don't want some goddamn spoon bender telling me what to do.
雷，我们家里有捣蛋鬼！
Ray, we have got a poltergeist!
警察一定能够摆平
Well, it's nothing that the police can't handle.
我是班尼斯特
Bannister.
林斯基医生，我马上过去
Dr. Lynskey, I'm on my way.
灵魂到访过的痕迹，每年这时都有这种问题
Persistent residue of the departed. Always a problem this time of year.
林斯基医生？
Dr. Lynskey?
谢谢你抽空过来　　这…
Yes. Thank you for coming. The...
问题到底出在哪里？
The activity is currently located where?
嗯，我也不知道，5分钟前才安静下来
Well, I don't know. It just went quiet about five minutes ago.
安静下来？
Went quiet?
餐桌是不是以逆时钟方向转？
The dining room table spun in a counterclockwise direction?
好像没有吧
I don't think that one happened. No.
马桶盖有没有上下翻动？
The toilet seat lid banged up and down?
没有
No.
床有没有飞起来？　有，我当时还在床上
Did the bed levitate? Yeah, with me on it.
无意识的意志力，喔，天哪
Spontaneous recurrent psychokinesis. Oh, boy.
这可能是我看过最糟的一件案子
This could be the worst case I've ever seen.
真的很糟糕
Yeah, this is bad.
好，各位，我可以帮你们赶鬼…
Okay. Well, folks, I can do a clearance...
不过费用可能会有点贵
but it's not gonna be cheap.
不过我可以提供6个月的保证
Although I do offer a six-month guarantee.
多少？
How much?
249元9毛5
$249.95.
不过午夜后的服务费用要再追加三成
But there is a 30% surcharge for making a house call after midnight.
还有车费、油资…
Then there's vehicle, gas...
所以总共的花费…
so I'd say the whole thing is gonna set you back...
大约是450元
somewhere in the neighborhood of $450.
不过可用你们前院的围篱来做抵销
Although we could forget about the fence, call the whole thing even.
快点啦
Do it.
好，不好意思，小姐，请后退一点
Okay. Excuse me, ma'am. You wanna stand back.
不想让你签弃权证书
I don't want you to have to sign a waiver.
外加1百元的材料费，我不能贴自己的钱吧
Plus $100 for materials. I can't be out of pocket.
班尼斯特，动作快一点
Just do it, for Christ's sakes, Bannister.
好了
Here we go.
好
All righty.
为什么是我们？他们为什么在我们家？
Why us? I mean, why are they in our house?
虽然鬼魂通常都在墓园里…
All I can tell you is emanations are normally confined to the cemetery...
不过他们会逃跑
although they do escape.
通常都是年轻的鬼魂
It's usually the young ones.
拜托你，班尼斯特
For God's sakes, Bannister, come on.
快一点
Come on.
这是圣水
It's holy water.
这简直是狗屁，根本就是狗屁
This is bullshit. This is total bullshit.
快点，太好了！
Come on. Yes!
这些是你们的
Okay, these belong to you.
抓到6个鬼魂
Six ectoplasmic emanations.
别担心，他们不会逃走
Don't worry. They can't escape.
有些人喜欢纪念品，想要我放在哪儿？
Some people like a souvenir. Where would you like me to put them?
不了，我们不需要留下做纪念
No. I really don't think we wanna hang onto those.
谢谢你
So, thank you.
需要吗？　　我才懒得管
Do we, hon? I could give a rat's ass.
好
Okay.
别担心，他们没知觉
Don't worry, they can't feel a thing.
起码书上是这样写
At least that's what it says in the book.
不过也不是绝对的
You never really know for sure.
好，谢谢你，班尼斯特，你可以走了
All right. Thank you, Bannister. You can go.
你在看什么看？
What the hell are you staring at?
怎么会有号码？
What's with the number?
什么号码？
What number?
要是你想吓我，一点用也没有
Look, if you're trying to freak me out, it's not gonna work, okay?
你知道他想干嘛吗？
You know what he's trying to do?
他只想骗我们的钱
He's trying to get more money out of us is what he's trying to do.
快点把你的东西拿走，给我滚出去
Here, take your shit and get the hell out of my house.
快点
Come on.
快点　　雷，你…
Move. Ray, just...
真是谢谢你
Thank you so much.
拿去吧　　谢了
There you go. Thanks.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你干嘛每次都这样对别人？
Why do you always have to alienate everybody?
我好像要吐了
I think I'm going to throw up.
糟糕
Damn.
老兄，那车厢有够烂！
Man, I hate that trunk!
我知道，我可不想让你们…
Yeah, I don't want you guys spreading your ectoplasmic muck...
把我的车弄脏
all over my car seats.
真是太为难你了，要不是因为我们…
Ain't that a bitch. The ectoplasm's the only thing sticky enough...
你的车早就散了
to hold the damn car together.
法兰克，我知道你的车很烂…
Look, Frank, I'm sorry about your pus yellow, piece-of-shit Volvo...
不过我们拒绝坐在车厢里，听到了没？
but we ain't riding in the damn trunk no more, you understand?
我们想时髦一点
We would like to cruise with some style, man.
你们今晚根本没帮我
You know, you guys left me high and dry tonight.
我到他们家的时候，什么事也没发生
I get to the house, nothing's happening.
不可思议
I couldn't believe it.
史都华，你到底想怎样？
Stuart, in or out?
你们连马桶盖都没碰？
You guys didn't even bang the toilet seat lid?
让我糗死了
You made me look like an asshole.
法兰克，我们抬床的时候，还扭到腰
We strained our backs lifting that heavy ass bed, Frank.
还有，是哪个白痴…
Yeah. Who was the idiot...
在他的头上写数字？
who put the number in the guy's forehead?
一点也不好笑
It wasn't funny.
快点做工…
Start pulling your weight, guys...
不然就送你们回墓园
or you're going back to the cemetery.
法兰克，你最好想一想
Yeah, well, you can pull this, Frank.
我准备要跟你算帐
I'm about to go like Jesse on your ass.
我要去找其他的黑人鬼魂…
I'm gonna find me some other black ghosts...
然后举办一场大游行
and then organize a march.
非裔美籍幽灵联盟
The African American Apparition Coalition.
简称非美幽盟
The AAAC.
法兰克，你给我听好！
And I'm gonna tell you something, Frank!
一群不爽的死黑人…
There ain't nothing worse than a bunch of pissed off brothers...
是很恐怖的！
that's already dead!
可以帮我一下吗？
Would someone help me, please?
史都华，放轻松一点，我是说真的
Stu, man, you got to loosen up, man. I'm serious.
来，放轻松
Come on, Stu, loosen up.
放轻松点，听到没？
Loosen up. Okay, you loose? All right.
神经不要那么紧绷嘛
So tight you can you play pick-up sticks with your butt cheeks.
放轻松，让自己变成微粒物体
Loosen up. Just particlise. There you go.
哇靠
Damn.
他根本就在占我们的便宜
That fellow takes us totally for granted.
我们应该是他的工作同仁
And we're supposed to be his business partners.
搞什么嘛，我明早一定要修理他一顿
What a joke. I'm gonna straighten him out first thing in the morning.
我可是双学位的高材生
He's dealing with a double major here.
我不再当好好先生了，一定要给他颜色瞧瞧
Well, no more Mr. Nice Guy. I'm gonna get rough.
史都华，你在跟我说话吗？　不是
You talking to me, Stuart? No.
史都华，那是你的问题，你对他太好了
See, Stuart, that's your problem. You're too soft with him.
你只要到法兰克面前，看着他的眼睛说…
You gotta just walk up to Frank, just look him in the eye and say:
“法兰克，照我说的做，不然你就死定了！”
"Frank, give me what I want or I'm gonna bust your ass!"
法兰克，你怎样啊？
Yo, Frank, how's it hanging?
赛瑞斯，我也不知道，你觉得呢
I don't know, Cyrus. You tell me.
老实跟你说，你实在没什么本钱
Well, Frank, I'll tell you the women ain't missing nothing.
我之前就说过了，不要从水管冒出来
Come on. I told you guys, stay the hell out of my plumbing.
别这样啦
Look. Come on, Frank.
我们需要开会，我们得好好谈一谈
Look, we wanna call a meeting, man. We gotta rap.
赛瑞斯，我要尿尿…
Cyrus, I gotta take a leak...
我要就地解决了
and I'm not getting out of the shower.
再见
Goodbye.
所以，快乐的鬼魂就是有出息的鬼魂
Therefore, a happy ghost is a productive ghost.
为了达到那境界，我整理出了几项建议
To that end, I've drawn up a list of suggestions.
法兰克，别忘了…
Now bear in mind, Frank...
我们为你忠心地服务了5年
that we have given you five years of loyal service.
苍蝇，史都华，你们就只会带来苍蝇
Flies. That's what you've given me, Stuart. Flies.
为什么苍蝇老是跟着你们跑？
Why is it that flies stick to you guys like shit to a blanket?
法兰克，你真幽默
Very funny. You a funny guy, Frank.
只会为自己着想
You know, all you think about is yourself.
我也想发发牢骚
You know, I can complain, too, you know.
我想买新衣服，你一天到晚都穿得很帅
I would like some new clothes. You get to dress nice.
我看起来却俗得要死
Here I am still looking like Linc from The Mod Squad.
谁叫你70年代就挂了
You died in the '70s. It's a bummer.
法兰克，我想赛瑞斯想说的是…
I think what Cyrus is attempting to say, Frank...
我们觉得这个企业并没有…
is that we don't feel that the enterprise is evolving...
照原先的计划来发展
in quite the manner in which we all agree.
防虫药
我跟你说话时…
Please don't reach through me...
请不要伸手穿过我身体
when I'm trying to speak to you.
法兰克，我们来谈雪茄的事
Now, Frank, we gotta talk about cigars.
雪茄？　　没错
Cigars? Damn right.
你明明就答应过我，要送我一盒雪茄
You've been promising me a box for I don't know how long.
赛瑞斯，我不想伤你的心，但你作古了
Cyrus, I hate to break this to you but you're dead, you know.
不可能抽雪茄
You can't smoke.
你还是可以点燃一支，再把烟往我脸上吹啊
Well, you can light them up and blow the smoke in my face.
要是我点雪茄，我一定会吐在你脸上
If I light up a cigar, I'll blow my lunch in your face.
大家趴下！法官，该死！
Everybody, get down! Damn it, Judge!
把枪放下
Put the shooters away.
法兰克，他对我头部开枪，置我于死地
That was a head shot, Frank. He could have killed me.
要是我想每天被枪击的话…
You know, if I wanted to get shot at every day...
我早就搬到洛杉矶去了
I'd move my black ass to Los Angeles!
当一个人的下巴掉下来时…
When a man's jawbone drops off...
就应该重新评估局势
it's time to reassess the situation.
我帮自己在墓园找到了…
I got myself a nice little grave...
一个不错的小地方
up there at the cemetery.
我差不多该入土安息了
It could soon be time to lay my bones.
法官，你是我的帮手，没你我的生意也别做了
No, you're my go-to guy. Without you, I'm out of business, Judge.
吓人…
Frightening...
是年轻人的工作，法兰克
it's a young man's game, Frank.
我体力不够了
I ain't got no more hauntings left in me.
你在胡说什么？你明明就…
What are you talking about? You're in...
硬朗得很
great shape.
我的关节都快散了
My joints are getting powdery.
我的脸也快散了，我根本就要解体了
The dog's running away with my face. Hell, I'm falling apart.
你这么多年来都是如此
You've been falling apart for years.
千万别告诉他们…
Don't go saying nothing to the boys...
不过我的鬼魂就快枯干了
but my ectoplasm is all dried up.
法官，那真是太遗憾了
I'm sorry to hear that, Judge.
法兰克，省省吧
Give it up, Frank.
不能靠死亡这行讨生活啦
Death ain't no way to make a living.
法官，我得把这房子修好
Yeah, well, Judge, I gotta finish this house.
你不可能把这房子修好
You ain't never gonna finish this house.
你什么也做不成！
You ain't never gonna finish nothing!
法兰克，不要再骗自己！
You're fooling yourself, Frank!
你惹过太多麻烦了
Too many skeletons in the closet.
法兰克，是我们啦
It's us, Frank.
你觉得怎样？很恐怖吧？
What do you think? Pretty scary, huh?
下次不要再这样了
Don't you ever do that again.
下次或许可以用白床单
Say, maybe we should try a white sheet next time.
老兄，我听到白这个字就不爽
Ain't gonna be no white sheets, bro.
赛克，早安　　法兰克
Good morning, Zack. Frank.
你们想谈一谈，那我们就来谈一谈
Okay, you guys wanna talk, let's talk.
来谈谈这个吧，这是我银行写来的信
Let's talk about this. This is a letter from my bank.
要是付不出1万5，他们就要把这房子卖了
This says they want $15,000 from me or they're gonna sell my house.
不错啊
Well, cool.
我们也该离开这鬼地方…
It's about time we ditched this drafty-ass crib...
搬到一个有漂亮窗户的新家了
and moved to someplace nice with some glass in the windows.
赛瑞斯，事态很严重，懂吗？
Cyrus, this is serious shit, okay?
这是我的房子，我才不要让给别人
This is my house. I'm not losing it.
史都华
Stuart.
史都华，那只鸡一点也不吓人…
The chicken. The chicken was not scary, Stuart...
看起来很蠢
the chicken was stupid.
法官，帮帮我吧
Judge, help me out here, okay?
跟他们谈一谈，他们都很尊敬你，谢了
Talk to these guys. They look up to you, all right? Thanks.
各位，我急需1万5千
I need $15,000, guys. I need it quick.
该去好好吓人一番了
It is time to get seriously scary.
你看过房子四周吧？
So you checked the place out, right?
对　　好
Right. Cool.
里面有几个？　　5个
How many we got in here? Five.
他们绝不会起疑心
They won't suspect a thing.
一群呆瓜根本搞不清楚状况
Poor suckers, they won't even know what hit them.
有几个出口？　　2个
How many exits? Two.
我们得把握机会，一定要狠点，绝不留情
All right, man, this is it. We gotta be hard. No mercy.
我们要跟演员一样专业
We're going in like professionals, like Charles Bronson.
没听到尖叫声之前，绝不罢休
We don't stop till the screaming starts, you dig?
我知道了
I'm with you.
走吧
Let's go.
好
Yeah.
去吓人吧
Let's kick some ass.
来吧，一、二、三…
Here we go. One, two, three...
早安，我的宝贝们，你们好
Good morning, my darlings. Hello.
沃特豪太太，信都在桌上
The mail's on the table, Mrs. Waterhouse.
谢谢，席维雅
Thank you, Sylvia.
席维雅，妈今天要来吃午餐，快收拾一下
Sylvia, Mother is coming for lunch. Pick up, quick.
是的，太太
Yes, ma'am.
亲一下
Big kiss.
不要到处乱跳，像个小婴儿一样
All right, kid, quit jumping around and acting like a baby.
这是很严肃的
This is serious.
我们要把你爸妈吓到屁滚尿流
Now, we're gonna scare the living daylights out of your parents.
你要帮我们吗？
So, come on, kid, you gonna help us out?
是不是跟我们一国？
Are you with us?
看到没？他都懂，小孩最聪明了
See? He gets it. The kids always get it.
来吧　　好
Let's go. All right.
沃特豪太太
Mrs. Waterhouse.
沃特豪太太！
Mrs. Waterhouse!
糟糕，这个刚才便便了
Damn. Here, man. This one did le poo-poo.
离我远一点　　天哪，他们有够小…
Get it away from me. Man, they're so little...
大便却臭得要死
but their doo-doo smells like old shoes.
沃特豪太太！
Mrs. Waterhouse!
我的宝宝！
My babies!
是，我是法兰克班尼斯特
Yeah, Frank Bannister.
马上就到
I'm on my way.
法官，你得跟我一起去
Judge, I need you riding shotgun.
太好了
Yes.
该死！快点走啊
Damn it! Come on, let's go.
快点开啊
Come on. D for drive.
法兰克，四处看看，你难道不知发生什么事？
Look around you, Frank. Don't you realize what's happening?
知道啊，路上大多是灵车
Yeah, every other car is a frigging hearse.
快点，我要到镇上去
Come on, I can't even get across town.
这城镇有麻烦了
This town is in deep trouble.
太多葬礼，太少交通号志
Yeah, too many funerals, not enough traffic lights.
法兰克，死神又来了
It's Death, Frank.
在我们中间
Death is amongst us.
快点啦，时间就是金钱
Come on, let's go. Time is money.
你根本没在听我说话！
You haven't heard a goddamn word I've said!
小子，我还以为你很特别…
I thought you had some character, son...
照现在看来，可不是那么一回事
but right now you're not showing me much.
法官，你说得没错，看好罗
You're right, Judge. Watch this.
小心点
Look out.
法官，怎么啦？你看起来脸色苍白
What's the matter, Judge? You look a little pale.
太棒了
Beautiful.
法官，太棒了，这一定轻松到家
Beautiful, Judge. This is gonna be easy.
你好好休息一下吧？我马上就回来
Why don't you just rest your bones? I'll be right back.
太太
Ma'am.
灵魂到访过的痕迹
Persistent residue of the departed.
每年这个时候都有这种问题
It's always a problem this time of year.
我是法兰克班尼斯特，你有打电话来
Frank Bannister, I believe you called.
立刻就到府上服务，我的天哪
Not a minute too soon. Oh, boy.
法兰克，她…　闭嘴
Frank, she just... Shut up.
法兰克，没有用，她…
Frank, it's no use. She...
太糟糕了
This is bad.
无意识的意志力
Recurrent spontaneous psychokinesis.
这可能是我见过…
Yeah, this could be the worst case I have ever...
地方骗子常出没于墓园
最糟的一件
...seen.
班尼斯特先生，不好意思，打电话麻烦你
I apologize for calling you, Mr. Bannister.
请离开
Please leave.
你到底想搞什么鬼？
What the hell are you trying to do to me?
利用受害者家属，实在是很低劣
Preying on the bereaved is about as low as you can go.
班尼斯特先生，你是个害虫，大众应该警觉
You're a parasite, Mr. Bannister, and people should be warned.
我有权利服务大众
Yeah, well, I got a right to offer my services to the public.
要是你没注意到…
In case you hadn't noticed...
镇上居民现在面临很严重的健康危机
we are in the midst of a major health crisis.
费尔沃特镇更不需要…
The last thing the people of Fairwater need is some...
你这种不要脸的小瘪三，利用死人来…
two-bit charlatan promising to pass on bogus messages...
欺骗无辜民众
from the other side.
不好意思
Now, if you will excuse me.
我只想讨生活　　生活？
I'm just trying to make a living. Living?
班尼斯特先生，你又懂什么生活？
Not a word you'd know a lot about. Is it, Mr. Bannister?
费尔沃特时报
小心点
Easy.
混蛋
Asshole.
你没事吧，老兄？
You all right, buddy?
你摔得真惨
Man, you took quite a fall.
班尼斯特！　　是
Bannister! Yeah.
听着，我需要帮助
Listen, you gotta help.
他们要把我埋了，你得帮帮我
They're gonna bury me, man. You gotta help.
班尼斯特，我怎么搞的？
Bannister, what is happening to me?
雷，你死了
Well, Ray, you appear to be dead.
别这样说，那是不可能的，我身体好得很
Don't say that. That's impossible. I'm in the prime of my life.
我每天都健身，我太太还是个医生！
I work out every single day. My wife's a goddamn doctor!
你为什么不走通道？　什么通道？
Why didn't you take the corridor? What corridor?
生命的通道，到另一个世界的通道
The corridor of life. The passageway to the other side.
因为我不想去另一个世界！
Because I don't belong on the other side!
老天爷啊，我才29岁
Jesus Christ, I'm only 29.
Hey, hey, hey.
雷…
Look, Ray...
放轻松一点
just relax, all right?
告诉我发生了什么事
You wanna tell me what happened?
我本来在划船机上…
I was on the rowing machine...
然后我的心脏突然间…
and then suddenly I felt this viselike grip...
一阵抽痛，然后我无法呼吸
just squeezing my heart and I couldn't breathe, Frank.
完全不能呼吸…
I just couldn't breathe and...
我吓坏了，我需要一点维他命B
I've got the shakes now. I need some vitamin B.
你不能再吃维他命了
Yeah, you can't take vitamins anymore.
你不能吃，不能喝，不需要上洗手间
You don't eat, you don't drink, you don't go to the bathroom.
一切都结束了
All that shit's over with.
你在一年内，一定要走到…
In about a year's time you're gonna get a chance...
通道另一头
to go through the other side again.
成为灵魂
To become what's known as a pure spirit.
不过现在你算是在地上游走的幽魂…
But in the meantime, you're what's known as an earthbound emanation...
基本上就是一团像云雾的物体…
which is a rotting cloud of bioplasmic particles...
能够渗过各种空隙
dripping ectoplasm from every orifice.
雷，冷静点
Relax, Ray.
好，班尼斯特…
All right, Bannister...
我得赶去自己的葬礼，可不可载我一程？
can you at least give me a ride so I don't miss my funeral?
好，雷，听着
Okay, Ray, listen up.
墓园不安全，知道吗？所以小心点
The cemetery is not a safe place, all right? So stay close.
班尼斯特，等等，我想听听他们在说什么
Later, Bannister. I want to hear what they're saying about me.
不要担心，他们不会伤害你
Don't worry about them. They're not gonna hurt you.
这儿到底发生了什么事？
What in the hell is going on out here?
快点回到坟墓里去！
Get back in your graves!
你这个畜…　　天哪！
Son of a... Holy Jesus!
法兰克班尼斯特！　去吧，我来就好
Frank Bannister! Go ahead. I'll handle this.
你在我坟墓上做什么？
What the hell are you doing in my graveyard?
给我离远一点！
You have been told to stay away!
给我像个男人一点！
Sound off like you've got a pair!
海尔，不要这么激动
Yeah, well, it's a public place, Hiles.
我不喜欢你！
I do not like you!
你不可以任意带鬼到这儿来！
You cannot bring your spooks in here without my permission!
快滚，败类！
Disappear, scumbag!
班尼斯特，我可不是什么游魂
I am not one of your shitty little emanations, Bannister.
你根本对付不了鬼魂
You cannot push spirits around.
你这个大败类！用鬼来吓人！
You are scum! Using spooks to put the frighteners on people!
让我觉得很恶心！
That makes me physically ill!
这儿有很多幽魂！
We got a lot of lowlifes around here!
要是有麻烦，我立刻行动！
And I will provide an armed response at the first sign of trouble!
不准给我离开！
They must be contained!
海尔，待会见
Catch you later, Hiles.
我还剩85年！
My tour of duty runs another 85 years!
班尼斯特，你在这也有一片烂墓地！
There's a piece of dirt up here with your name on it, Bannister!
我等你回来，你这个小懦夫！
I'm waiting for you, you little maggot!
有时候，有人认为雷不够慷慨…
There were times when people have accused Ray of being...
不过我相信他的内心深处…
less than generous, but I'm sure, deep down...
一定是非常仁慈和大方
the man possessed a heart of gold and a generous spirit.
是真的
It's true.
他不会说谎，在这种时候绝不会
He wouldn't lie. Not at a time like this.
因为神呼召了我们的兄弟雷…
Because God has chosen to call our brother Ray...
回到天家…
from this life to Himself...
我们将他的身体放入大地
we commit his body to the ground.
尘归尘，土归土
Earth to earth, ashes to ashes, dust to dust.
天哪，真是浪费
Jesus, what a waste.
愿神保佑看顾他　　真是个悲剧
The Lord bless him and keep him. It's a goddamn tragedy.
愿神给他安慰，让他安息主的怀抱
The Lord lift up His countenance upon him and give him peace.
雷，再见
Goodbye, Ray.
甜心，别哭了
Sweetheart, don't cry.
喔，糟糕！
Oh, shit!
法兰克！
Frank!
我知道你听得到
I know you can hear me.
班尼斯特，救我出去
Get me out of this hole, Bannister.
法兰克
Frank.
求求你，救我出去　　法兰克，你好
Get me out of this hole, please. Hiya, Frank.
嘿，华特　　没想到会看到你
Hey, Walt. Kind of surprised to see you.
出公差吗？　　不算是
Here on business, I guess? Not exactly.
班尼斯特，他们要活埋我
Bannister, they're gonna bury me alive in here.
我知道你和林斯基在他死前那晚…
I understand you and Lynskey had a little run-in...
起了点小争执
the night before he died.
事实上，除了他太太…
As a matter of fact, apart from his wife...
你是最后一个看到他的人
I believe you were the last person to see him alive.
华特，应该是你在出公差吧
It sounds like you're the one who's here on business, Walt.
不是，联邦调查局很关切这些命案
No.
The FBI is very concerned about these deaths.
看似是心脏病，但验尸时却发现…
They look like heart attacks but when they slice these people open...
他们的血管一点问题也没有
their arteries are just clean as a whistle.
不过心脏却曾经承受极大的压力…
But there's been this tremendous pressure on the heart...
就像被活活掐死一样
like the life has just been crushed right out of it.
法兰克，有什么解释吗？　班尼斯特！
You got any theories, Frank? Bannister!
不介意我最后看他一眼吧？
Mind if I pay my last respects before they fill him in?
不，抱歉
No. I'm sorry.
班尼斯特，求求你
Bannister, please.
我需要找点乐子
I need to be cheered up.
班尼斯特先生？
Mr. Bannister?
班尼斯特先生，你想见我吗？
Mr. Bannister, did you want to see me?
喔，我的天哪，她看得到我
Oh, my God, Frank. She can see me.
我想雷可能有托话给你
I thought perhaps you might have a message from Ray.
告诉她，告诉她我在这儿，告诉她
Tell her. Tell her I'm here, Frank. Tell her.
大家都说你是个骗子…
I mean, everyone says that you're a fraud...
不过我知道你是认真的
but I've seen what you can do.
法兰克！
Frank!
你一定觉得我很蠢
You must think I'm very stupid.
不好意思
Excuse me.
露西…
Lucy...
雷说他很爱你
Ray says he loves you very much.
这边请，桌子在这儿
Here you are. Here's your table.
你好　　你好
Hi. Hi.
雷跟我们在一起吗？
Is Ray with us?
对
Yeah.
说她今天看起来很漂亮
Tell her she looks great.
他说你今天看起来很漂亮
He says that you look great.
说是我说的　　是雷说的
Tell her they're from me. Oh, those are from Ray.
今天是我们的周年庆
It's our anniversary.
对了，他说今天是你们的周年庆
Right. He says it's your anniversary.
雷在我身边吗？
Is Ray beside me?
他在这儿
He's over here.
你们今晚好吗？
Greetings. How are you this evening?
想喝点酒吗？
May I offer you some wine?
露西，你想喝点白酒还是红酒？
I don't know. Lucy, do you want some, what, red, white?
红酒，我们每次都喝红酒
Red, we always have red.
白酒，我从来都不喜欢喝红酒
White. I've never been fond of red.
露西！
Lucy!
你以前是建筑师？
So you used to be an architect?
很久以前　　班尼斯特，安静点
A long time ago. Can it, Bannister.
她不想听你的生平故事
She doesn't want to hear your life story.
你自己盖的房子？
Wow. So did you build your own house?
一定是你的梦想屋吧
I mean, you must have a dream home.
可以算是吧
You could call it a dream home.
甜心，我一回到现实世界…
I'm gonna build you a dream home, sweetheart...
就帮你盖一个梦想屋
just as soon as I get on my feet.
最好是啦
Yeah.
为什么你看得到雷，而我却不行？
Tell me, why is it that you can see Ray and I can't?
我5年前出了一场意外…
I was in an accident, a car accident...
一场车祸
about five years ago.
我不知道，他们说…
I don't know. They say that...
人经历一场浩劫后…
sometimes when you have a traumatic experience...
想法会有所改变
that it can alter your perception.
所以你能看到灵魂？
Really, so after that you could just see spirits?
发生什么事了？
I mean, what happened?
要跟雷说话吗？不然我来这就没意义了
How about you talk to Ray? That's why I'm here.
我终于能参与这场谈话了，太好了
Finally, I'm in the conversation. Terrific.
我真的有一个很重要的问题…
Well, actually I do have an important question...
想要问雷
that I have to ask Ray.
他听得到你
Well, he can hear you.
雷，我想知道你把我所存的…
Ray, I really need to know where you invested my money...
1万6千元投资到哪去了
the $16,000 that I had saved.
律师都找不到
The attorneys can't seem to find it anywhere.
糟糕，做生意失败了
Shit. I blew it on a bad investment.
不要告诉她，让我想一想
But don't tell her that. I'll think of something.
露西，钱都没了，不见了，他生意失败
It's gone, Lucy. It's gone. He blew it on a bad investment.
你这个混蛋！
You asshole!
告诉她不会有事的
Tell her everything's gonna be okay.
我一定会照顾她，我会搬回老家
I'm gonna look out for her. I'm gonna move back into the house.
快告诉她　　我才不要说假话
Tell her that. No, that's not a good idea.
班尼斯特，这不关你的事
Bannister, this doesn't concern you.
雷在说什么？他在说什么？
What's Ray saying? What's he saying?
他离开了，雷离开了
He left. Ray left.
他说他很抱歉，不过他想让你静一静…
He said he was sorry, but he wanted to leave you alone...
好好开始过生活
let you get on with your life.
班尼斯特，我向天发誓，我会杀了你
I swear to God, Bannister, I'm gonna kill you.
真不敢相信…
I can't believe it, I mean...
雷就是这样，拿了钱就跑…
That's just like Ray to just take the money and run. I...
班尼斯特先生，我和雷彼此之间…
Ray and I haven't been honest with each other...
早就失去了坦诚
in a long time, Mr. Bannister.
并不算是一段美好的婚姻
It wasn't what you would call a good marriage.
你这个婊子！
You bitch!
露西，没关系
Lucy, it's gonna be okay.
把你的臭手拿开！
Get your hands off my wife!
该死！
Goddamn it!
对不起
Sorry.
班尼斯特，我可以乱动东西
I can move shit, Bannister.
你最好小心一点
Man, you better watch your back.
我最好清理一下，马上回来
I better clean this up. I'll be right back.
这儿食物不错吧？
Good food, huh?
是啊，很好吃
Yeah, it's great.
妈！
Mom!
看起来又像是心脏病…
Looks like another heart attack...
不过在验尸报告出来之前，不能确认
but I can't confirm it till the autopsy.
该死
Damn.
服务生说发现尸体前5分钟…
The waiter says he saw this guy coming out of the john...
看到一男子从洗手间走出来
about five minutes before the body was found.
那是谁？　　法兰克班尼斯特
And who might that have been? Frank Bannister.
他当时脸色苍白，全身发抖
He was as white as a sheet and shaking.
服务生以为他不舒服　　该死
Waiter thought he'd been sick. Damn.
嗨，露西　　露西？
Hi, Lucy.
Lucy?
别过来
No.
林斯基医生替我工作，我们是同事
Dr. Lynskey works for me. We're colleagues.
医生，她是很重要的证人
Look, Doc, she's a material witness, all right?
好
Okay.
华特，有人在停车场看到班尼斯特
Walt, Bannister was last seen in the restaurant parking lot.
他离开时车开得很快
He took off at high speed.
带他过来
Bring him in.
你看看
Look at that.
你死去的先生跟你在餐厅一起用餐？
So your dead husband was having dinner with you at the restaurant?
他点了什么？
What did he order?
失陪一下
Oh, God. Excuse me.
提米
Timmy.
提米，请到前面柜台
Timmy, front desk, please.
谢谢
Thank you.
露西，这位是联邦探员米顿迪墨
Lucy, this is Special Agent Milton Dammers of the FBI.
我坐火车来的
I came by train.
我本来要坐飞机，不过我不太喜欢飞机
I was going to take the flight but I didn't feel good about the plane.
请问班尼斯特…
At what time precisely...
到底什么时候离开洗手间？
did Bannister leave for the bathroom?
你
You.
我不太确定
I'm not sure, precisely.
他吃饭的时候，有没有用很多盐巴？
Did he use excessive amounts of table salt during his meal?
什么？　　回答问题
What? Answer the question.
拜托一下，很晚了
For Christ's sakes, it's really late.
我根本记不得
I can't remember that, okay?
搞什么嘛？
Oh, God. What is this?
露西，不好意思，我马上回来
Excuse me, Lucy, I'll be right back.
米顿？
Milton?
抱歉，警长
Sorry, Sheriff.
我很讨厌女人的尖叫声
I have a problem with women yelling.
米顿，需要帮忙吗？
Milton, can I get you anything?
派瑞警长！
Sheriff Perry!
你侵犯到我的私人空间
You are violating my territorial bubble.
露西，我知道你很难过
Lucy, you're still grieving.
易受到法兰克班尼斯特这种人的利用
It would be very easy for a man like Frank Bannister to take advantage.
你的心眼怎么这么小，真是不可思议
You have such closed minds. I can't believe it.
我反对
I object.
特务探员迪墨先生…
Special Agent Dammers...
有超过20年的办案经验…
has over 20 years experience in the area...
对于超自然心理学很有研究
of paranormal psychology.
他花很多时间在不同教派…
Much of that was spent undercover with various...
和团体间做卧底
cults and sects.
林斯基太太，我看过太多疯狂的事了
I get all the fruity cases, Mrs. Lynskey.
米顿，你可不可以进来坐下？
For God's sake, Milton, would you come inside and sit down?
我比较喜欢站着，谢谢你
I'm more comfortable standing. Thank you.
这件事跟法兰克班尼斯特毫无关系
I really don't see what this has to do with Frank Bannister.
林斯基太太，你并不了解法兰克班尼斯特
Mrs. Lynskey, you know nothing about Frank Bannister.
你宣称他是真正的灵媒…
You claim he's a bona fide psychic...
不过我听到的却是胡言乱语
yet all I've heard is a lot of ill-informed, meandering waffle.
1990年7月3日…
On the third day of July 1990...
法兰克班尼斯特当时是位成功的建筑师…
Frank Bannister, then a successful architect...
忙着新家的工程
was overseeing the construction of his new home.
建筑商雅各普莱兹事后确认…
Now, the building contractor, Jacob Platz, would later confirm...
班尼斯特那天早上的确喝了酒
that Bannister had been consuming alcohol that morning.
晚间12点23分，普莱兹看到班尼斯特…
12:23 p. m., Platz sees Bannister...
和他太太黛布拉在吵架
in a heated argument with his wife, Debra.
据说班尼斯特答应，要帮黛布拉在新家…
It appears that Bannister had promised Debra a garden...
盖一座花园…
in the new home...
不过后来未经她同意…
and then, without consulting her, proceeded to lay...
就铺下10公分高的水泥…
a four-inch thick concrete slab...
为自己盖了一座篮球场
creating a basketball court for himself.
12点31分…
12:31 p. M...
普莱兹看到他们夫妻俩驾车离去
Platz watches the couple drive away.
班尼斯特的后车厢有一个工具盒
Bannister kept a tool box in the back of his car.
里面装有万用弹簧小刀
And in it was a utility knife with a retractable blade.
班尼斯特那天早上…
Bannister purchased seven new blades...
在三街和嘉耐街转角的…
that morning...
莱森建筑工具店…
at Jesson's Hardware Store and Building Supply...
买了不少新的刀片
on the corner of 3rd and Garrett. 3rd and Garrett.
7月3号
Third of July.
7把刀片，3
Seven blades. Three.
米顿…
Milton...
你在喃喃自语，我们根本听不懂
you're mumbling. We can't understand a word you're saying.
中午12点33分…
12:33 p. M...
他们开着84年代的富豪汽车往山上去
and their '84 Volvo heads into the hills.
那是他们最后一次一起出游
It is the last time anyone will see the couple together.
当时班尼斯特和太太不断争吵…
Now, by Bannister's own admission, the argument continues to rage...
吵到不能再吵时，黛比拉叫班尼斯特停车…
reaching a climactic point when Debra demands that Bannister stop...
靠边停，让她下车
pull over, let her out.
就在那一刻，晚上12点36或37分…
And at that moment, probably 12:36, 12:37 p. M...
车子在急转弯处冲出马路…
the car leaves the road on a sharp curve...
都因为班尼斯特开得太快
presumably because Bannister was driving too fast.
所以她死了？
She was killed?
她飞到车子14公尺之外
Her body was found some 15 yards from the car.
而班尼斯特…
Now, Bannister...
2个小时后，在树林中被警方找到
he was picked up two hours later, wandering in the woods.
他宣称车祸发生后…
He claimed to have no recollection of the events that occurred...
就完全失去了记忆
after the accident.
林斯基太太，不过很奇怪的是…
But here's the odd thing, Mrs. Lynskey.
他的万用小刀不见了
His utility knife was missing.
至今都没被找到
And to this day it has not been found.
你们知道还有什么怪事吗？
But do you know what was really bizarre?
黛布拉的额头上…
Debra's corpse had the number 13...
刻有13号的字样
carved into its forehead.
不吉祥的数字
Unlucky for some.
拜托，你疯了
Come on. You're out of your mind.
你说的根本是虚构人物
You're talking about a mythical figure.
12世纪的假冒宗教领袖
A pseudo-religious icon from the 12th century.
小子，别再说一堆没大脑的废话了
Save your pea brain prattle for the classroom, boy.
那明明是死神…
That was the soul collector...
他一向以杀人为乐
and he's been taking people out since time began.
他要在费尔沃特镇大开杀戒…
He's going about some dark business here in Fairwater...
我们只不过是饵
and we ain't nothing but worm bait.
时候到了，死路一条
When your number's up, that's it.
又有人死了
There's another one gone.
古埃及之秘密
费尔沃特博物馆证物防腐保存
他不见了
He's gone.
班尼斯特先生，我们不会给你钱
There's no money for you here, Mr. Bannister.
你是下一个
You're next.
你在吓我吗？
Are you threatening me?
不，我不是那意思
No, that's not what I'm saying.
他想要杀我　　放轻松，好吗？
He's threatening to kill me. Just relax, all right?
听我说…　　他想要把我给杀了
Just listen to me and... He's threatening to kill me.
班尼斯特！　　太好了
Bannister! Great.
好　　不好意思
Okay. Excuse me.
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
不好意思
Excuse me. Excuse me.
把枪拿开好吗？　　不要动
Put the gun away, all right? Freeze.
各位，请放松
All right, everybody, just take it easy.
班尼斯特，不要动，不要动
Just stay there, Bannister. Just stay there.
好险
Yes.
好极了
Great.
我成功了
I did it.
法官
Judge.
班尼斯特，不要动
Bannister, stop.
看来我不是用空包弹
Looks like I ain't shooting with blanks no more.
真是太美了
Mighty fine woman.
牙齿很漂亮
Good teeth.
把手放在讲台上　　法官
Now put your hands on the podium.
不要动！
Judge. Stay down!
法官大师可不是白叫的
They don't call me the hanging judge for nothing.
不要动
Stay right there.
小心点
Heads up.
接得好
Good catch.
不要动！
Freeze!
泰斯，好枪法
Good shooting, Tex.
她本来又年轻又美丽！
And she was so young and beautiful!
我最喜欢她们这样躺好
I like it when they lie still like that.
好重
This is heavy.
我觉得青春无比
My juices are flowing again.
法官！
Judge!
班尼斯特！
Bannister!
法兰克，快点离开
Go, Frank. Just get out of here now.
混蛋！
Bastard!
先走一步
Gotta go.
班尼斯特！　　不要动
Bannister! Stop.
Whoa! Whoa!
该死，快点啊
Damn. Come on.
贺乐威路
趴下去，不要起来
Just get down. Get down and stay down.
喔，不
Oh, no.
麦姬达！　　不！
Magda! No!
听我说
Listen to me.
不！
No!
喔，不
Oh, no.
你这个混蛋，你杀了我！
You killed me, you bastard!
你这个变态，这样会让你得到快感吗？
You're sick. Is this how you get your kicks?
你觉得杀死我很爽吗？
Did it feel good killing me?
班尼斯特，你觉得杀死你太太很爽吗？
Bannister, did it feel good killing your wife?
你这个杀人魔！
You're a murderer!
我想他应该逃不远，边界到处是警察
I don't believe he'll get very far. We've got the state line covered.
派瑞警长…
Sheriff Perry...
我想我们该不会再看到班尼斯特先生了
I seriously doubt we will see Mr. Bannister any time soon.
他比你想像中的更厉害
The man is resourceful beyond anything you can comprehend.
哈罗，法兰克　　嗨，华特
Hello, Frank. Hi, Walt.
我想向你们报告麦格达瑞斯琼斯的…
I've come to report that Magda Rees-Jones'...
遗体在和乐卫街上…
body is lying near my car...
在我的车子附近
off Holloway Road.
法兰克，你和她的死有没有什么关系？
Frank, did you have anything to do with her death?
法兰克！
Frank!
法兰克，你还好吗？发生什么事了？
Frank, are you okay? What happened?
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
你要逮捕他吗？　林斯基太太，请别插手
Are you arresting him? Please leave, Mrs. Lynskey.
法兰克，你需要找律师
Frank. Frank, you need a lawyer.
露西，快回家
Go home, Lucy.
但你什么也没做，他什么也没做
But you haven't done anything. He hasn't done anything.
你怎么知道？
How do you know?
你认识我吗？
Do you know me?
露西，我是好人吗？因为…
Am I a nice guy, Lucy? 'Cause...
餐厅的那件事根本就是狗屁，因为…
that cozy little scene in the restaurant was bullshit, 'cause...
那不过是我的工作
I was doing my job.
我才不在乎你，我不在乎任何人
And I don't give a damn about you. I don't give a damn about anybody.
你在胡说什么？　　快回家
What the hell are you saying? Go home.
好了
Okay.
露西，你能开车吗？　　可以
Lucy, are you okay to drive? Yeah.
想玩亲亲吗？
Got a kiss for honey bunny?
我知道，我知道我看起来很恐怖…
I know, I know. It's the way I look. It's this...
看起来像鬼魂
damn ectoplasm stuff.
让你觉得很恶心对不对？
It turns you off, doesn't it?
露西，别这样，你根本没在听我说话！
Come on, Lucy, you're not listening to me!
宝贝，你明明知道我们的感情很好
Look, baby, you know we have a great relationship.
只不过…
It's just that...
我觉得你最近好像都心不在焉
lately I don't feel that you've been giving 100%.
这镇上现在有一股我从来没见过的…
There has been a destructive force unleashed on this town...
恶势力在猖狂
such as I have never seen.
目前死亡人数高达…
We have a body count of...
28人
twenty-eight.
班尼斯特先生，你是个危险人物
You're a very dangerous man, Mr. Bannister.
拜托…
For Christ's sake...
你该不会觉得班尼斯特跟这些…
you're not seriously suggesting that Frank is responsible for...
派瑞警长，你不会懂的
You're way out of your depth here, Sheriff Perry.
请离开
Please leave.
法兰克班尼斯特是我的囚犯
Frank Bannister is my prisoner.
美国总统给予我的权力…
By the power invested in me by the President of the United States...
我警告你…
I am telling you...
快点离开这里
to get the hell out of this room.
你有听过妮娜库拉吉娜吗？
Have you ever heard of Nina Kulagina?
1970年3月10号，妮娜库拉吉娜利用意志力…
March 10, 1970. Nina Kulagina with the power of her mind...
让一只青蛙心跳暂停
stopped the beat of a frog's heart.
这个实验的纪录目前收藏在…
The record of this experiment is currently held...
圣匹兹堡当地一位叫…
in the files of Prof. Gennady Sergeyev...
沙利格夫教授那儿
of Saint Petersburg.
沙利格夫在研究这个实验…
And as Sergeyev interpreted this cardiogram...
他觉得心脏因为瞬间…
it seemed to him that the heart had experienced...
增加的电流而负荷不支
a sudden flare-up of electrical activity.
妮娜库拉吉娜想杀死小动物…
The heart imploded, the arteries burst...
所以让它的心脏在体内爆炸，血管破裂
and all because Nina Kulagina wanted the animal dead.
我不杀人
I don't kill people.
一部份的你以为如此
There's a part of you that believes that.
法兰克，另一部份的你…
There's another part of you, Frank...
却早已失控
that's out of control.
你那具有破坏力的冲动
Your destructive impulse.
我看过穿着袍子的身影
I've seen a figure in a cape.
我看过他伸手到人们胸口，对他们心脏施压
I've seen him reach into people's chests and squeeze their hearts.
是谁？
Who was it?
死神
Death.
我能够通灵
I can communicate with the other side.
我有阴阳眼
I can see spirits.
我不知道为什么，我也不懂
I don't know why. I can't understand it.
班尼斯特先生，你觉得自己很特别是吧？
You think you're quite unique, don't you, Mr. Bannister?
不过我做这一行，看过太多像你的人了
But in my business, I deal with your type every other week.
这个死神…
This Death figure...
不过是为了满足…
is nothing more than a homicidal alter ego...
你内心想杀人的冲动
that satisfies your compulsion to kill.
不是
No.
每次你想杀人的时候…
Every time you want to take somebody out...
死神就会出现并替你动手
Death figure suddenly appears, does the job for you.
这只是你掩饰罪恶感的一种防卫功能
It's your rational mind's way of absolving yourself of guilt.
不是！
No!
法兰克，你几时有了阴阳眼？黛布拉死后？
When did you first start seeing spirits, Frank? After Debra's death?
你杀了你太太
You killed your wife.
才没有！
No!
1985年起，我就开始研读…
I have studied the coroner's reports...
费尔沃特镇上的每一份验尸报告
of every death in Fairwater since 1985.
28宗死亡案都跟心脏病有关
Twenty-eight cases involved crushed hearts.
动脉被掐到爆裂
Arteries choked until they burst.
从1990年你美丽的…
That started in 1990 with your...
太太黛布拉开始
beautiful wife, Debra.
她是第一个受害者
She was the first.
雷林斯基
Ray Lynskey.
你跟他吵了一架，3小时后，他就死了
You have an argument with him, three hours later, dead.
我们都知道你不喜欢麦格达瑞斯琼斯
Magda Rees-Jones, we know you didn't like her.
洗手间那位先生呢？
But what about the guy in the toilet?
法兰克，他有冒犯你吗？
What did he do to you, Frank?
在你的皮鞋上尿尿吗？
Piss on your Hush Puppies?
你为什么在颤抖？
Why are you shaking?
喔，我的天
Oh, my.
你现在又犯了，对不对？
My, my, my. You're doing it right now, aren't you?
你现在想把我给杀了
You're trying to kill me. Right now.
班尼斯特，想都别想
Forget it, Bannister.
我有穿铅制背心！
I'm wearing a lead breastplate!
镇上有28宗不解的死亡案
We have 28 unexplained deaths here.
你猜我怎么想？
You know what I think?
我觉得你跟每一起死亡案都有关
I think you are involved in each and every one of them.
这边请
Buddy, this way.
不
No.
脱内裤？天哪，搞什么鬼？
Man! Pulling your drawers off? Man, what the hell?
班尼？
Benny?
我的老兄班尼，这是我兄弟班尼
My man, Benny. Stu, it's my boy here, Benny, man.
班尼，说真的，我是你朋友
Benny, but I'm your friend, man, seriously.
记得要用肥皂洗澡
Three words, shower with soap.
快点
Come on.
你没事吧？　　抽筋
You all right? Spasm.
没事
It's all right.
法兰克！　　法兰克，问题大了
Frank! Frank, we got problems.
他们要告你涉嫌重大罪行
These guys are gonna stitch you up on a capital offence.
他们要把费尔沃特镇上所有的…
All these murders that have been going on in Fairwater...
谋杀案都怪到你头上
they're gonna pin them on you.
我和史都华要救你出去，快来
Stu and I are gonna get you out of here. So come on, man, let's go.
法兰克？
Frank?
法兰克，快点啦　　等一下
Frank, come out of it, man. Wait, no, wait.
喔，天哪！算了，史都华
Oh, God! Forget it, Stu.
看看他
Look at him.
他失去信念了
He doesn't believe anymore.
就快好了
It won't be long now.
他快到承认阶段了
He's reached the acceptance stage.
面对内心的罪恶感
Grappling with his guilt.
寻找答案
Seeking resolution.
迪墨探员，你要知道…
You realize, Agent Dammers...
我们没有任何控告他涉嫌杀人的证据
we have no forensic evidence linking him with any of the deaths.
没关系
Doesn't matter.
我想还没审判前，他应该就会自杀了吧
I expect this case to suicide long before it ever reaches trial.
每次都会这样
They always do.
什么梦想屋嘛
So much for the dream home.
露西，你在这儿搞什么鬼？
What the hell are we doing here, Lucy?
看看这个鬼地方，乱七八糟
I mean, look at this place. It's a dump.
他真是个大败类
God, this guy's a loser.
喔，我的天哪，露西
Oh, my God, Lucy.
你看看
Look at this. Look at this.
露西，他耍我们，他骗了我们
He set us up, Lucy. The man set us up.
这是我们家！
This is our house!
露西，他把我们当呆瓜看待
He took us for a couple of schmucks, Lucy.
你看，露西
Look, Lucy. Look.
完美的篮球场就这样毁了
Perfectly good basketball court gone to pot.
我是班尼斯特
Yeah, Bannister.
班尼斯特先生，你一定要帮我
Mr. Bannister, you've got to help me.
我女儿派翠亚安布莱德利在跟恶魔通灵
My daughter, Patricia Ann Bradley, is communing with the evil one.
她一煽动，他就会出现
He's in this house at her instigation.
救救我，把他们赶走
Help me. Help me drive them out.
露西，我想知道你为什么拒绝我
Lucy, I gotta know why you keep shutting me out.
我还是有很多…
I still have a lot to...
露西！
Lucy!
派翠亚
Patricia.
林斯基医生
Dr. Lynskey.
派翠亚，你还好吗？
Patricia, are you all right?
是你妈妈下的手对吧？
It's your mother, isn't it?
你妈妈一直在伤害你
Your mother's the one who's been hurting you.
她需要帮助，派翠亚，她精神不正常
She needs help. She's delusional, Patricia.
你不能再住在这儿
You can't go on like this.
你不懂
You don't understand.
不！
No!
谋杀案发生后，我爸爸自杀
My father killed himself after the murders.
妈妈总说是我的错
Mother says it was my fault.
所以我得把他的骨灰供在我房间
So I have to keep his ashes in my room.
喔，天哪
Oh, my God.
她说我很邪恶…
She says I'm evil...
就像强尼那样
just like Johnny.
跟我到妈妈的房间去
Come with me to Mother's room.
杀手受审
致命鸳鸯在医院夺走12条命
巴特利受刑
派翠亚布莱德利，谋杀案帮凶？
这不是你
This isn't you.
不是现在的你
This isn't who you are now.
是强尼
It was Johnny.
他发了疯
He went crazy.
我逃不出他的掌心，我以为他要杀了我
I couldn't get away from him. I thought he was gonna kill me.
派翠亚，你得离开这间房子
Patricia, you have to get out of this house.
过全新的生活
You can start over.
我妈来了，快点躲起来
It's Mother. Please hide. Please.
我带她到厨房去
I'll take her to the kitchen.
你待会儿再溜出去
You sneak out later.
你在我房间做什么？
What are you doing in my room?
我听到可疑的声音
I thought I heard a noise.
妈妈，我帮你煮点咖啡
I'll make you some coffee, Mother.
妈妈，咖啡准备好了
Mother, coffee's ready.
露西，快走
Lucy, go.
法兰克
Frank.
副警长，谢谢你
Thank you, Deputy.
林斯基医生，需要的时候再叫我
Just call me when you're done, Dr. Lynskey.
好
Yes.
法兰克，听我说，我找到你的刀了
Frank. Frank, listen to me. I found your knife.
被藏在布莱德利太太的衣柜里
It was hidden in old lady Bradley's closet.
法兰克，她疯了
She's crazy, Frank.
你并没有伤害任何人
You haven't hurt anybody.
法兰克，你是个好人
You're a good person, Frank.
别这样
Don't do this.
拜托别这样
Please don't do this.
天哪，你以为自己是世界上…
Jesus, do you think that you're the only person...
唯一失去过亲人的人吗？
who's ever lost somebody?
你装得一副没有感情的样子…
God, you walk around like you don't have any feelings...
你只不过是害怕
but the truth is that you're just scared.
你真的很虚伪，为什么要这样？
You're a goddamn hypocrite. Why are you doing this?
法兰克，你到底在怕什么？
What are you afraid of, Frank?
露西，我不想伤害你
I don't want to hurt you, Lucy.
少给我胡说
That's crap. Don't give me that.
看着我
Look at me.
我到外面好了，这样好像是抓到爸妈在嘿咻
No. I'll be outside. This shit is like walking in on your parents.
好，我到外面去，我现在就…
Right. Right. Yeah, I'll just be outside. I'll just...
法兰克，怎么了？　　小心点！
What is it, Frank? Look out!
你这个畜生
You son of a bitch.
发生什么事了？
What's happening?
抓住他！
Grab him!
发生什么事了？
What's happening?
好，听我说
Okay. Listen. Listen to me.
快点去叫副警长，冷静一点
Call for the deputy and try to sound calm.
副警长，我要走了
Deputy, I'm ready to leave now.
史都华，他去哪了？　我好像抓到他了
Stuart, where did he go? I think we got him.
糟糕
Shit.
不，你这个畜生！法兰克，快出去！
No, you son of a bitch! Get out, Frank! Go!
法兰克！
Frank!
往这里
This way. Go.
班尼斯特，不要动！　好
Freeze, Bannister! All right.
救命　　我抓到你了
Help. I got you now.
请你救救我，他已经疯了　　好
Please help me. He's gone crazy. All right.
后退点
Stay back.
给我看好…
Now...
法兰克，快点！
Frank, come on!
快点，法兰克！快点出去！快点！
Go, Frank! Get out of here! Please! Now!
法兰克，快点走！
Frank, let's go!
这边，快点
No, this way. Come on.
糟糕！
Shit!
法兰克，那牢房里有什么？害我心脏不舒服
What was that in that cell, Frank? I felt something crushing my heart.
露西，我打不过他，我也不能保护你
I can't fight him, Luce. I can't protect you.
只有一个解决的方法
There's only one way to deal with this thing.
我得要有灵魂出体的经验
I got to have an out-of-body experience.
什么？　　现在就需要
What? And I got to have it right now.
不！
No!
露西，走开，请走吧
Go away, Luce. Just walk the other way.
等一下
Wait. Wait.
这会让你的心跳减慢，体温降低
This will slow your heart rate and lower your body temperature.
你只有20分钟
You'll have 20 minutes, max.
超过时间就会损害细胞
Any longer than that and there's a danger of tissue damage.
不知道我能不能把你救活…
That's only if I can successfully revive you...
没有保证
and there's no guarantee.
法兰克…
Frank...
别这样
you don't have to do this.
露西，你最好把门关起来
Lucy, better close the door.
快一点
Hurry up.
不会太久
It won't take long.
冷冻中
林斯基医生，没想到你对低温学有研究
I didn't know you had an interest in cryogenics, Dr. Lynskey.
我9点要把他救回来　　为什么要这样做？
I'm reviving him at 9:00. Why would we want to do that?
露西
Luce.
Lucy.
Whoa.
好了
There we go.
混蛋，放我走！
Let me go, you bastard. Let me go!
混蛋，放我出去！快点让我下车！
Let me out now, you bastard! Let me out of this car now!
我觉得墓园…
I find cemeteries very...
是个非常宁静的地方，不是吗？
restful places, don't you?
快点转，带我回去
Turn this car around and take me back.
林斯基太太，我一定会
I intend to, Mrs. Lynskey.
11点准时
In exactly 11 hours time.
你这个畜生！
Son of a bitch!
不
No.
我认识查理
I knew Charlie.
史霸农场，1969年
Spahn Ranch, 1969.
我的第一个任务
My first assignment.
我做他们家的性奴隶…
I was the Family's sex slave...
长达六个月…
for six months. Six months...
为了服务我的国家…
in the service of my country...
而装成肮脏的嘻皮
disguised as a filthy hippie.
我要出去！
I want out!
让我下车！你快给我回来，大变态！
Let me out of here! Come back here, you creep!
我全身都写着痛苦的回忆
My body is a road map of pain.
1974…
1974...
路西弗的孩子
Children of Lucifer.
三年的埋伏…
Three years undercover...
还要喝羊血
drinking goat's blood.
1981…
1981...
我渗透死亡教派
I infiltrated The Cult of the Dead.
我参与食人仪式…
I was involved in ritualistic cannibalism...
酒神祭礼…
in orgiastic dances reaching...
体验过情欲的痛苦
painful thresholds of intense physical eroticism.
忍受了极度的痛苦
I have withstood excruciating pain.
不过我不会被打倒
But I will not be broken.
我为国牺牲…
I have suffered for my country...
露西
Lucy.
不过痛苦…
But pain...
是有代价的
has its reward.
意志力…
The power of the mind...
有绝对的力量
is absolute.
法兰克
Frank.
法兰克，是你吗？
Frank, is that you?
是我做的？
I'm doing this?
我能够用意志力开车？
I'm making the car move with the power of my mind?
太好了！
Yes!
不
No.
等一下！
Wait!
给我回到地下去…
Get back in the goddamn ground...
你这个什么都不懂的灵媒白痴！
you unorganized grab-asstic gob of teleplasmic shit!
你是什么鬼东西？好像一副很厉害的样子
Who in the hell are you? Sound off like you've got a pair!
嘿，混蛋
Hey, asshole.
你是谁？
Who are you?
强尼巴特利
Johnny Bartlett.
我以为你这种人会在地狱被火炼 法兰克，我逃出来了
I thought guys like you fried in hell. I got out, Frank.
我这几年来都很努力，得分超过40
I've been carrying on the good work. Got me a score of 40.
哈利圣克莱尔
Harry Sinclair.
我只想和帮我报仇的英雄握个手
I just want to shake the hand of the man who finally avenged my death.
你头上有号码
You've got a number.
我死的时候，巴特利在我额头上刻的
Bartlett carved it into my forehead as I lay dying.
我是最后一个
I was the last.
法兰克，他大错特错了吧？
He couldn't be more wrong, could he, Frank?
糟糕！
Shit!
No. No!
不！不要用
No! Don't use it.
不
No.
法兰克，呼吸
Frank. Okay. Just breathe.
慢慢呼吸
Breathe slowly. Breathe.
你没事了
Okay. You're okay.
好，法兰克
Okay. Frank.
好，露西，快点
All right, Lucy, come on.
1百毫升的利多卡因
A hundred milligrams of lidocaine.
快点给我1cc的肾上腺素
Get me one cc of adrenaline, quick, now.
我没抓到他　　谁？
I didn't get him. Who?
法兰克，你没抓到谁？
Who didn't you get, Frank?
强尼巴特利
Johnny Bartlett.
他回来了
He's back.
这是他的幻觉，过一下就好　　露西…
He's hallucinating. It'll pass. Lucy...
他又在杀人
he's killing again.
派翠亚
Patricia.
露西，你得把她从屋里救出来
Lucy, you got to get her out of the house.
快点！
Go!
派翠亚！
Patricia! Patricia.
听我说，我们得逃出去
Listen to me. We have to get out of here.
派翠亚从不出门
Patricia never leaves the house.
布莱德利太太，很抱歉，她非走不可
I'm sorry, Mrs. Bradley, but she's coming with me.
你根本搞不清状况，她是我女儿，快上楼
You have no right. She's my daughter. Get upstairs.
不行，不能再这样继续下去
No. Look, this is gonna stop now.
你在讲什么？
What are you talking about?
你衣柜里怎么会有法兰克班尼斯特的刀？
Why do you have Frank Bannister's knife in your closet?
你进我的房间？
You went in my room?
妈妈
Mother.
派翠亚
Patricia.
妈妈现在想去找警察
Mother wants to go to the police now.
不…
No...
她马上就下来了
she'll be down in a few minutes.
派翠亚，我们现在就得离开
No, Patricia, we have to go now.
这里不安全，强尼巴特利又回来了
It's just not safe here. Johnny Bartlett's back.
我知道
I know.
他晚上都会来找我
He visits me at night.
我不知道他为什么会来
I don't know why he comes.
他会虐待我
He torments me.
他为什么要来？
Why has he come?
我要被处罚吗？
Am I being punished?
派翠亚，快点，我们现在得马上离开
Patricia, please. Let's just go now, please.
派翠亚，我现在就想杀她
I wanna kill her now, Patty.
这样我们就有41个
That'll give us 41.
比盖西还多8个
That's eight clear of Gacy.
再9个就能打破邦帝的纪录
Another nine and we'll have broken Bundy's record.
不敢想像，他知道时会有什么表情
I can't wait to see old Ted's face when he hears the news.
好！
Yes!
什么？
What?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我们应该等妈妈的
We really should wait for Mother.
那个白痴灵媒今天真的很扫兴
And that asswipe psychic nearly ruined it for us tonight, Patty.
让我们出糗　　派翠亚，你不会有事的
He made us look stupid. You're gonna be okay, Patricia.
一切都会平息　　闭嘴
Everything's going to be all right. Shut up.
那个俄国食人魔到处炫耀…
That Russian cannibal creep's running around...
说他杀了50几个人
saying he did 50 plus.
派翠亚，那让我们很难堪耶
That reflects badly on the both of us, Patty.
这记录应该由美国人来保持
This record should be held by an American.
我同意
I quite agree.
你想要的话…
You can come...
可以跟我一起住
stay with me if you like.
宝贝，我现在就要把她杀了
I'm going to kill her now, baby.
好
I'd like that.
我去拿外套
I'll just get my coat.
你这个假腥腥的婊子！
Patronizing do-gooder bitch!
派翠亚…
Patricia...
你把她杀了，我来观赏
you kill her, I'll watch.
准备好了？
Ready?
宝贝，我最喜欢你这样了
I love it when you do that, baby.
布莱德利太太？
Mrs. Bradley?
布莱德利太太，你要跟我们一起走吗？
Mrs. Bradley, are you coming with us?
喔，我的天哪
Oh, my God.
露西！
Lucy!
不是那边！
No, not that way!
天哪，露西
Jesus, Lucy.
约翰查尔斯巴特利
喔，我的天哪，这是强尼巴特利的骨灰
Oh, my God. These are Johnny Bartlett's ashes.
什么？
What?
我们得把这些拿到另一边去
We gotta get these to the other side.
什么？
What?
我们得拿到教堂去
A church. We got to get them to a church.
老医院里面有一间小教堂
There's a chapel. There's a chapel in the old hospital.
好
All right.
不！
No!
从这边走　　好
No, let's go down here. Okay.
该死
Damn it.
看到门了没？　　有
Look there. You see that door? Yes.
不要担心，听到我的信号再出来
It's all right. Come out when I say.
我上去看看　　好
I'm gonna look up there. Okay.
露西？
Lucy?
好极了
This is great.
法兰克？
Frank?
医生，不好意思，我们在找12号房
Excuse me, Doctor, we're looking for Ward 12.
走楼梯到四楼…
Go up the stairs to the fourth floor...
就在走道的右边
down the corridor to your right.
就在小教堂对面　　谢谢你
It's just opposite the chapel. Thank you.
我请人来帮忙，清洁工
I'll get someone to help. Orderly.
清洁工，你聋了吗？
Orderly, are you deaf?
I said, Orderly, are you deaf?
蠢蛋！
Moron!
看来你是第一个
I guess that makes you number one.
趴下！
Get down!
法兰克，你没事吧？
Frank, are you okay?
小教堂在四楼
The chapel's on the fourth floor.
法兰克，小心！
No, Frank, watch out!
我们得快离开，快点！
We gotta go. Go!
露西
Lucy.
你们都一样
You're all the same.
等一下！
Wait!
不！露西！
No! Lucy!
小子，把枪放下，警察马上要到了
Put the gun down, son. The law is on its way.
派翠亚，得几分了？
What's the score, Patty?
11分
Eleven.
跟史达魏德一样
That's the same as Starkweather's.
我们现在平手
We have a tie on our hands.
露西　　法兰克
Lucy. Frank.
卡住了
It's jammed.
快拿去，快点　　好
Take it. Just take it. Right.
我马上就回来，不要乱跑
I'll be right back. Don't go anywhere.
不
No.
还给我　　让我来猜
Give that to me. Let me guess.
你得把这些骨灰放在神圣的地方…
You have to get these ashes to consecrated ground...
才能把邪灵赶走
in order to destroy the forces of evil.
把骨灰瓮给我！
Give me the goddamn urn, Dammers!
这些骨灰绝对不能曝光
Under no circumstances must these ashes ever be released.
不！
No!
Oops.
你真是不懂事情的严重性
You have no idea what you've just done.
法兰克，你根本就不懂吧？
You just don't get it, do you, Frank?
你心理明明就有病，所以才会把…
Your pathological mindset has made it necessary...
自己的缺陷看成…
for you to interpret your sad personal inadequacies...
正义与邪恶之间的搏斗…
as a grand struggle between good and evil...
这一切都是为了让你自己得到安慰
in order to gratify your pathetic need for self-glorification.
你真是个混蛋
You are such an asshole.
没错，我是带有鸟兹冲锋枪的…
Yes, I am. I'm an asshole...
混蛋
With an Uzi.
起来！
Get up!
真令人觉得恶心！快起来！
You make me sick! Get up!
转身，我不想从背后对你开枪
Turn around. I don't want to shoot you in the back.
转身！给我快转身！
Turn around! I said, turn around!
我以美国政府的名义…
As an agent of the United States Government...
命令你立刻转身
I am ordering you to turn around.
法兰克！
Frank!
求求你不要伤害我
Please, please don't hurt me. Stop.
拜托
Please.
法兰克！
Frank!
喔，我的天哪，法兰克
Oh, my God. Frank.
黛比拉
Debra.
你杀了她
You killed her.
老兄，你是下一位
You're next, pal.
宝贝，把他杀了
Take him out, baby.
不！快动手！
No! Get him!
不！住手！
No! Stop!
法兰克！
Frank!
不！
No!
派翠亚，快点
Get him, Patty.
太好了，宝贝
Yeah, baby.
你真有天分
Baby, you are an artist.
而且很漂亮　　不！
You're pretty, too. No!
不
No.
这样才对
Yes.
我想来解剖小动物
I'm in the mood for a little vivisection.
不！
No!
我也是
Me, too.
你这个婊子！
You bitch!
不！
No!
强尼，我抓到你的女朋友了！
I got your girlfriend, Johnny!
快点来救她啊！　　该死！放开她！
Come and get her! No, goddamn you! Let go of her!
强尼！　　快点来救她，胆小鬼！
Johnny! Come and get her, you coward!
快来救她！　　不！
Come on and get her! No!
放开派翠亚！
Let go of my Patty!
派翠亚！
Patty!
强尼！
Johnny!
过来，抓紧我的手
Come here. Give me your hand.
Whoa.
法兰克，再见，你死定了
See you later, Frank. We got you.
我们要去杀人！
We're going back down to get us some more!
法兰克
Yo, Frank.
还好吧？
How's it going?
拜拜，法兰克
Bye, Frank.
强尼
Johnny. Johnny.
法兰克，后退　　对
Step back, Frank. Yeah.
应该会蛮惨不忍睹的
This isn't going to be pleasant.
通往地狱的直达公车不需排队，不需等待
The old express bus to hell. No lines, no waiting.
很不可思议吧？
It's really something, isn't it?
最棒的图书馆
Excellent libraries.
最高级的雪茄
Premium cigars.
还有辣美眉
And of course, the honeys.
不错吧？史佬在这儿可是美眉杀手
Yeah, how about that? Stu's a regular chick magnet up here.
法兰克，你好
Hello, Frank.
该回家了
It's time to go home.
我已经到家了
I am home.
错
No.
官方机构告诉我们…
You see, the authorities have informed us...
你的时候还没到
that it's just not your time.
老兄，享受生命吧
Start living, dude.
开心一点
Be happy.
法兰克！
Frank!
我得告诉你一件事
There's something I have to tell you.
什么？
Yeah?
不好意思打扰你们　　没关系，华特
Sorry to interrupt you, folks. It's all right, Walt.
法兰克，你对谍仙有多少了解？
Frank, what do you know about Ouija boards?
不太懂
Not a lot.
我在布莱德利家找到一大叠
I found a whole stack of them up at the Bradley house.
看来派翠亚5年前出狱时…
It looks like Patricia just got herself a direct line...
就跟死去的男友连上了线
to her dead boyfriend as soon as she was released five years ago.
听说老太太…
It seems like the old lady...
知道派翠亚涉嫌杀害你太太之后…
when she got wind of Patricia's involvement...
就对派翠亚下迷幻药
in your wife's death, then she just kept the girl sedated.
不过她阻止不了巴特利
She just couldn't stop Bartlett, though.
华特，这个结局还不错，叙述得很精彩
Nice epilogue, Walt. It was well delivered.
法兰克
Frank.
还有一件事
Just one other little thing.
我马上就要开始休长假了…
I got a whole bucket load of vacation time coming to me...
不知道我们…
and I thought you and I...
能不能一起编写有关这件事的书
could collaborate on a book about all this.
说不定我就可以退休了
It could be my ticket off the force.
我不太会写作
That's not really my area.
要是需要找人合作…
If you're looking for a collaborator...
何不请你的护身天使帮忙？
how about your guardian angel over there?
法兰克，我被你耍了　　没错，华特
You got me, Frank. I got you, Walt.
警长-费尔沃特镇
法兰克，改天见
I'll see you, Frank. Bye-bye.
他看起来好像真的很不爽
Boy, that Dammers, he sure looks pissed.
是啊
Yeah.
法兰克，有时候…
Well, sometimes, Frank, you see...
在一场大浩劫之后…
when you go through a traumatic experience...
人的想法会有所改变
it kind of alters your perception.
别闹了
No.
Whoa!